A Guide to the Julia Cooley Altrocchi Papers, 1940-1962
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Julia Cooley Altrocchi Papers 1940-1962
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10795
This collection consists of 7 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Provenance
This collection was transferred from Rare Books on October 17, 1988.
Contents List
- Manuscript
  - "Astronaut to Vega," a poem by Julia Cooley Altrocchi 1962 April, TMs, 6 p. on 6 leafs.
    Winning poem in $100.00 Dramatic Monologue in Verse Contest, sponsored by the Browning Society of San Francisco.
- Letter
  - Julia Cooley Altrocchi, Berkeley, California, to "Barrett Collection, University of Virginia," 1962 October 8, APCS
    Describes the material that was a gift to the Library.
- Photographs
  - Julia Cooley Altrocchi at the time of the publication of The Old California Trail 1940, Photograph
  - Julia Cooley Altrocchi 1962 May 9, Photograph
- Miscellaneous
  - Bibliography of Julia Cooley Altrocchi 1962, TMs, 19 p. on 19 leafs.
    Includes books and articles containing references to her, awards, and publications of her work.
  - Biography of Julia Cooley Altrocchi 1962, TMs, 1 p.
    Including a brief biography and synopsis of her published works.
- Audio Recording
  - Reading of "Astronaut to Vega" by Julia Cooley Altrocchi 1962 May 18, Tape
    Read at the annual San Francisco Browning Society Dramatic Monologue in Verse Contest, open to all writers of the San Francisco Bay Counties, aired on KPFA Radio in Berkeley, California on June 18, 1962.